http://www.pressenterpriseonline.com/terms

Skip to main content
Terms & Conditions I. WELCOMEWelcome to the PressEnterpriseOnline.com website (hereinafter 'Website'). Using this site tells us that you have read and agreed to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy detailed below. Please read the following sections carefully. If you do not agree with these terms, please exit this site. These Terms may change at any time in the future. No individual notice of changes will be provided.  You will be bound by any subsequent change to these Terms.II. CONTENTWe may change, suspend or discontinue availability of any aspect of the Website at any time. We may also impose limits, registration requirements or fees on certain features or services or restrict your access to parts or the entire Website without notice or liability.In addition, the Website may contain links to other Internet sites, resources, and sponsors or advertisers on the Website. We are not responsible for the availability of these outside resources, or their contents, and accordingly, you should direct any concerns regarding any link or other website to the site administrator or webmaster of such site. III. COPPAIn compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen nor do we knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to post content online absent a parent or legal guardian’s express written consent.IV. COPYRIGHTAll information, content, services and software displayed on, transmitted through or used in connection with the Website, including, but not limited to, news articles, reviews, directories, guides, text, photographs, images, illustrations, audio clips, video,  trademarks, logos and the like, are owned by Press Enterprise Inc., and/or its third party licensor.   Permission to copy or reproduce Press Enterprise Inc. materials may be sought by completing the reprint permission form at http://www.pressenterpriseonline.com/system/files/page-files/pe-reprint-request.pdf. V. DMCAClaims that Press Enterprise Inc. may have infringed on another’s copyright may be brought to our attention under the terms of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA") by providing:(i) A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of a copyright interest that is allegedly infringed;(ii) Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site;(iii) Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of the infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material;(iv) Information reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact you, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail address;(v) A statement that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and(vi) A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and made under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.Notice of the claimed infringement should be sent to copyright@pressenterprise.net VI. USER-PROVIDED CONTENTBy posting a message, uploading a file, providing information to, communicating with, or otherwise placing any material on our websites, you are granting Press Enterprise Inc. a royalty-free, perpetual, non-exclusive, unrestricted right and license to use, copy, modify, display, archive, store, distribute, reproduce and create derivative works from such information, in any form, media, software or technology of any kind now existing or developed in the future. All rights in this term are granted without the requirement for additional compensation of any sort to you and without further permission required. In addition, all contributions to this website must comply with the following rules:  You agree not knowingly submit any false, defamatory, abusive, obscene, threatening, racially offensive, sexually explicit or illegal material to the Web site.In posting comments on the contributions of others, you agree not to harass other participants.You may not submit information that is libelous or defamatory or that discloses private or personal matters concerning any person.You may not post information or links that are obscene or pornographic.You may not contribute information or pictures that violate the property rights of others, including unauthorized copyrighted test, images or programs, trade secrets or other confidential proprietary information, and trademarks or service marks used in an infringing fashion.
Content contributions solely focused on the promotion of commercial events or businesses are not permitted.You assert that the information and pictures you contribute are your own, are licensed to be uploaded and downloaded by other participants, are in the public domain, or are otherwise free of copyright or other restrictions. VII. ANONYMOUS POSTINGSUsers are encouraged, but not required, to use their real names when posting comments or opinions on the Press Enterprise Inc. discussion boards/chat rooms.  Users may use a pseudonym in lieu of their real name but are prohibited from impersonating another person or falsely misrepresenting an affiliation with any other person or entity.  Although Press Enterprise Inc., is under no obligation to maintain the secrecy or anonymity of any user, we reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to notify anonymous posters of any third party attempts to discover the real identity of an anonymous poster before disclosing the real identity or identifying information (such as an I.P. Address) to any third parties.   VIII. NO OBLIGATION TO MONITOR POSTINGSPress Enterprise Inc. does not endorse and is not responsible for any statement, opinion, advice given or made in any discussion forums. Your use of the Press Enterprise Inc. discussion forums is at your own risk. Press Enterprise Inc. is under no obligation to review discussion postings but  reserves the right in its sole discretion and for any reason to delete or redact any information or other content regardless of whether the information or other content violates the policies discussed herein. Further, Press Enterprise Inc. reserves the right to limit or terminate service to participants who violate these Terms.   Press Enterprise Inc. is not responsible for censoring or monitoring postings but reserves the right to enforce the policies outlined in this document, and reserves the right to move or remove notes at its sole discretion and without notice or explanation.  In no event will Press Enterprise Inc. be liable for any incidental, consequential, or indirect damages (including, but not limited to, damages for loss of business profits, business interruption, loss of programs or information, and the like) arising out of or in connection with Press Enterprise discussion forums, or any information or services provided on the Website.  IX. PRIVACY POLICYWe respect your privacy and appreciate the confidence you have placed in the PressEnterpriseOnline.com. We are committed to protecting your privacy and preserving your trust. Please carefully review this Privacy Policy to learn about how we collect, use, and protect any personal information you provide us and your choices for managing your personal information. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or if you wish to exclude your personal information from our direct marketing purposes, please feel free to contact us at: webmaster@pressenterprise.net.
We collect information that may personally identify you (such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information) only if you choose to share such information with us. For example, we may collect personal information from you when you register on the Web site, subscribe to one of our services, enter sweepstakes, contests or other promotions, and at other times. We also collect credit card information in connection with any purchase you make on or through the Web site. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you decide not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Web site or other services.
We may automatically collect non-personal information that does not identify an individual user, such as IP (internet protocol) address, ISP (internet service provider), the Web browser used to visit the Web site, the time the Web site is visited, which Web pages were visited on the Web site, a unique mobile device identifier (in connection with the use of the Web sites or related services from mobile devices) and other anonymous Web site usage data.
We also use cookies (a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your Web browser) and Web beacons (an electronic file placed within a Web site that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the quality of the Web site. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Web site may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Certain of our Service Providers (defined below) may use cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf, including, without limitation, ad serving.We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose personal information to third parties, without your permission, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
We use personal information and non-personal information for internal purposes, including:enhancing your experience at the Web site;performing administration and technical support for the Web site;enabling you to enter sweepstakes, contests and other promotions;enabling you to use certain services and features available on or through the Web site;creating aggregate information about demographics and usage patterns;inviting our promotional vendors and advertisers—with your permission—to call to your attention special offers, products and services that may be of interest to you; andenabling purchases of goods and services.We may use aggregate information to measure general Web site usage patterns and characteristics of our user base, and we may include such aggregate information about our audience in reports to our commercial vendors. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics (for example, a certain percentage of our users live in a certain area) without your permission in order to describe our audience to existing and prospective advertisers or other third parties. However, this aggregate information does not reference names, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, or other personal information, and it is not traceable to a specific recipient or user e-mail address.From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services including credit card processing, advertising, promotions, analytics tools, data management, Web hosting, and Web development. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. Each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of your information in order to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.We may work with third-party advertising companies which may use information about your visit to the Web site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you on the Web site and on third-party Web sites. From the Web site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons or pixel tags. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party advertisement serving company may collect from you. Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to Press Enterprise Inc. or its affiliates, or to others. We may also disclose your personal information when we believe the law or legal process requires such disclosure. Please note that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, may have the authority under certain circumstances to permit your personal information to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission.We use encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of personal information that you share with us. However, no data transmission over the Internet (or, with respect to our mobile services, over cellular phone networks) can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect personal information, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from the Web site, and you do so at your own risk.The Web site may contain links to Web  sites operated and maintained by third parties over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked Web sites may be different from our Privacy Policy. You access such linked Web sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked Web site before disclosing any personal information on such Web site.When you post messages or other user generated content, the information that you provide (including personal information) may be publicly available to, collected by, and used by third parties. We are not responsible for the content of such messages or images posted by users or such disclosures of personal information.We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, in whole or in part, by posting the changed Privacy Policy on the Web site with the date of the most recent change. Your continued use of the Web site constitutes your agreement to abide by the Privacy Policy as modified. If you object to any such changes, your sole recourse shall be to cease using the Web site.X. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY AND DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTYAlthough we try to provide accurate information on the Web site, the materials may contain inaccuracies, errors and typographical errors. Press Enterprise Inc. and its affiliates do not warrant the accuracy or completeness of the Content contained on the Web site. We may make changes to the content at any time without notice and make no commitment to update the content.YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU ARE USING THE SERVICE AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE WEB SITE, THE CONTENT AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH THE WEB SITE, AND THE SOFTWARE MADE AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH THE WEB SITE, IF ANY, ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, AND PRESS ENTERPRISE INC.  AND ITS AFFILIATES HEREBY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESSED AND IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTIES OF ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR ANY OTHER WARRANTY, CONDITION, GUARANTEE OR REPRESENTATION, WHETHER ORAL, IN WRITING OR IN ELECTRONIC FORM, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF ANY CONTENT CONTAINED THEREIN OR PROVIDED BY THE WEB SITE. PRESS ENTERPRISE INC. AND ITS AFFILIATES DO NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT ACCESS TO THE WEB SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR THAT THERE WILL BE NO FAILURES, ERRORS OR OMISSIONS OR LOSS OF TRANSMITTED INFORMATION, OR THAT NO VIRUSES WILL BE TRANSMITTED ON THE WEB SITE. PRESS ENTERPRISE INC. AND ITS AFFILIATES ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR USER CONTENT OR OTHER CONTENT POSTED BY THIRD PARTIES, ACTIONS OF ANY THIRD PARTY, OR FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT OR OTHER PROPERTY.YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT PRESS ENTERPRISE INC. AND ITS AFFILIATES, SUBSIDIARIES, SERVICE PROVIDERS, LICENSORS, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS OR EMPLOYEES SHALL NOT BE LIABLE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES FOR ANY INDIRECT, GENERAL, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY OR OTHER DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES (EVEN IF PRESS ENTERPRISE INC. OR ITS AFFILIATES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES). SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. ACCORDINGLY, SOME OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.XI. INDEMNIFICATIONYOU AGREE TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND AND HOLD HARMLESS, PRESS ENTERPRISE AND ITS AFFILIATES, SUBSIDIARIES, SERVICE PROVIDERS, LICENSORS, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS AND EMPLOYEES, FROM ANY AND ALL CLAIMS (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, CLAIMS FOR DEFAMATION, TRADE DISPARAGEMENT, PRIVACY AND INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY INFRINGEMENT) AND DAMAGES (INCLUDING ATTORNEYS' FEES AND COURT COSTS) ARISING FROM OR RELATING TO ANY ALLEGATIONS REGARDING: (1) YOUR USE OF THE WEB SITE; (2) PRESS ENTERPRISE INC. OR ITS AFFILIATES' USE OF ANY USER CONTENT OR INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU; (3) USER CONTENT OR INFORMATION POSTED OR TRANSMITTED THROUGH YOUR MEMBERSHIP ACCOUNT, EVEN IF NOT POSTED BY YOU; AND (4) ANY VIOLATION OF THIS AGREEMENT BY YOU.  PRESS ENTERPRISE INC. RESERVES THE RIGHT TO SELECT COUNSEL AND CONDUCT THE DEFENSE OR SETTLEMENT OF ANY SUCH CLAIM, WHICH SHALL NOT RELIEVE YOU OF YOUR OBLIGATION TO INDEMNIFY AS PROVIDED ABOVE.XII. TERMINATIONWe reserve the right, at our sole discretion, immediately and without notice, to suspend or terminate this Agreement, your registration for any program offered on the Web site, your ability to access the Web site, and to remove any User Content, for any reason, including without limitation any breach by you of this Agreement or conduct by you that we determine to be inappropriate. You agree that Press Enterprise Inc. and its affiliates shall not be liable to you or any third party for any suspension or termination pursuant to this provision.XIII. GOVERNING LAW AND VENUE The agreement regarding these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy has been made in and shall be construed and enforced in accordance with Pennsylvania law, without regard to its principles of the conflicts of law. Any action to enforce this agreement shall be brought in the federal or state courts for Columbia County, Pennsylvania, and you hereby waive any objections to such action or venue. XIV. LIMITATION OF ACTIONAny cause of action you may have relating  to the Website, Privacy Policy, or these Terms of Use must be commenced within one year after the claim or cause of action arises, or within the applicable Pennsylvania Statuteof Limitation, whichever is shorter, or such claim or cause of action is barred.XV. SEVERABILITY AND WAIVERIf any provision of these Terms of Use or Privacy Policy is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or any other term or condition. Contact UsQuestions concerning the PressEnterpriseOnline.com website, these Terms of Use, or the Privacy Policy can be sent to:WebmasterPress Enterprise Inc.3185 Lackawanna Ave.Bloomsburg, PA 17815webmaster@pressenterprise.net(570) 784-2121Effective Date: 6/21/2013
